{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_10_8DFM3R",
                "player_3_8DFM3R",
                "player_1_8DFM3R",
                "player_6_8DFM3R",
                "player_15_8DFM3R",
                "player_7_8DFM3R"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                10,
                3,
                1,
                6,
                15,
                7
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "stand",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    81.924,
                    7813.718,
                    1538.151,
                    0,
                    -84.995859811037,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    361.031,
                    8265.697,
                    1258.25,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    153.01,
                    8306.108,
                    1258.25,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    173.188,
                    7904.646,
                    1538.151,
                    0,
                    -101.16294172963377,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -21.873,
                    8376.383,
                    1258.243,
                    0,
                    -108.32090113793531,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -21.547,
                    8163.949,
                    1258.5,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -325.794,
            8042.199,
            1248.15
        ],
        "sample_radius": 922.3446861810505
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            393.917,
            7621.303,
            1538.151,
            0,
            117.82758955478597,
            0
        ],
        [
            -591.072,
            8465.581,
            1248.15,
            0,
            -24.677952575432155,
            0
        ],
        [
            0.488,
            8570.393,
            1250.83,
            0,
            -74.41752460805878,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is farther from the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many people are present in this ancient town?",
                "answer": "six"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many people are engaged in holding items?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many villagers are standing upright on the paths and walkways?",
                "answer": "five"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Counting by gender, how many men are visible among the people in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene have a bald head?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many bald men in the scene are also wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. pick up",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. carrying"
                ],
                "answer": "A. pick up"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. pick up",
                    "B. walking",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. standing"
                ],
                "answer": "A. pick up"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. lying",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. pick up",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. pick up"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Above"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Above"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Below",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. Slightly above and to the front-left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Slightly above and to the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. Above"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Below"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            }
        }
    }
}